

CONTACT

+62 81<u>3-101</u>8-1765

eldirb95@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/eldirb

https://github.com/eldirb21

JI Tarian Raya Timur blok O No 17, RT.11/RW.10, Kelapa Gading, Jakarta Utara 14250

PERSONAL SKILLS

BOOTSTRAP	80%
HTML & CSS	80%
JAVASCRIPT	80%
REACT NATIVE	90%
REACT JS	85%
VUE JS	80%
MYSQL	85%

LANGUAGES

INDONESIA	****
ENGLISH	****

CERTIFICATE

REACT NATIVE COURSE CERTIFICATION

BELADIRI BUULOLO

Software Developer



About Me

I've experience creating web and mobile applications for iOS and Android since 2020. Besides working full-time, I can work independently and respect a deadline. Adept at developing apps based on customer specifications recommending application changes to make programs more efficient and upgrading existing apps to make them more useful.



Education

2018 - 2022 Management Informatika

IPK. 3.2 Universitas Raharja

Office Administration 2011 - 2014

IP. 8.5 SMKS Kr. BNKP

Hilisimaetano



Experience

Sep 2022 - current Mobile Developer

PT Indocyber Global Teknologi (IGLO)

Building and maintaining Mobile Application for e-commerce scope.

Example: Mobbi - Jual Beli Mobil

Bekas using React Native.

Nov 2020 - Sep 2022 Software Developer

PT. Peksi Andaru Sakti Build and maintain Mobile & Web

Applications for internal company scope. Example: Andaru Collection, Andaru Delivery, Andaru Web uses

React Native, ReactJs.

Jul 2020 - Okt 2020

PT. Emco Digital Indonesia

Junior Programmer

Building and maintaining Web Application for expedition scope.

Example: Kargo - expedisi local

using React JS.